手袋
Handbag!
站住  等等  你的生命不只属于你
Stop! Wait! Your life is not your own!
别乱动它  明白吗
Keep your hands off it, do you hear me?
别动它  别动它
Off it. Off it.
不好意思  什么  你在说什么
Sorry? What? What are you talking about?
-你的裙子  -我的裙子
- Your skirt. - My skirt?
看看边角  我就是这么发现的
Look at the hem of it, that's what I noticed.
抱歉  我还在努力跟上我的脑子  它太快了
Sorry, I'm still catching up with my brain. It's terribly fast.
那些印记  你看到了吗
Those markings, you see them?
裙子被车门夹住时
You only get marks like that
才会留下那样的印记
by trapping the hem of your skirt in a car door,
但印记在你的左边
but they're on the left-hand side,
所以你没有开车  你坐在副驾上
so you weren't driving, you were in the passenger seat.
我坐出租车来的
I came in a taxi.
门外的街上并没有出租车在等
There is no taxi waiting in the street outside,